# ANDREA MOLNÁR

## **UX/UI** Designer

+39 339 591 6612

hey.andrea.molnar@gmail.com

andi-sketches.github.io/portfolio

Milan, Italy



I am a UX/UI designer in the making, with plenty of curiosity to learn more about the art of creating intuitive and beautiful designs. I also like to try my hand at coding up the results! See my portfolio on the above link. After completing my Bachelor's degree and 2 years of working in Product Marketing in Berlin, I decided to move to sunny Italy to enrol in the MSc program for Human-Computer Interaction at the University of Trento. As I'm finishing degree now, I'm open for internship opportunities.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Human-Computer Interaction, MSc**

University of Trento (Trento, Italy) | 2017 - 2019

HCI combines socio-cognitive, computer science and design knowledge to inform the design decisions in creating of digital user interfaces. Current GPA: 30/30. A selection of classes taken:

- Interaction design and social cognition
- Prototyping interactive systems

Affective computing

• User Experience Design

#### Media Management, BA

Macromedia University (Berlin, Germany) | 2012 - 2015

Thesis topic: "Gamification and Crowdsourcing in E-Learning: A Duolingo case study". Final GPA: 28/30. A selection of classes taken:

- Media Design and Technologies
- International Management
- Marketing and Advertising
- Media and Communication Project

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Junior Product Marketing Manager**

Babbel (Berlin, Germany) | 2016 - 2017

Founded in 2007, Babbel has developed the world's first language learning app. A leader in the digital language learning industry, it has over 1 million active subscribers. Key responsibilities included:

- Driving the research and development of new product features in collaboration with the User Research and Product Design, as well as coordinating their roll-out strategy;
- Assessment and analysis of the business potential of innovation opportunities based on market conditions, the competitive landscape and customer needs.

#### **Product Management Trainee**

Crobo (Berlin, Germany) | 2015 - 2016

Crobo is a full-service digital marketing agency, with a primary focus on mobile and online games. Key responsibilities included:

- Aid in designing features for crobo's in-house affiliate platform;
- Communication between the product team and the users of the platform (announcement of updates, processing feature requests and feedback etc.).

## **SKILLS**

#### **UX & UI Design Process**

Competitor analysis

User interview & analysis

Surveys

User research

Persona & user journey creation

Wireframing & IA

Prototyping

Usability testing

Agile development

#### **Tools & Code**

Sketch

Figma

InVision

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

## **LANGUAGES**

English (Fluent)

Italian (Fluent)

German (Fluent)

Hungarian (Native)

Japanese (Intermediate)

## **INTERESTS**

Drawing

Literature & Theater

Hiking